<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ignasia Consulting</title><link>https://ignasia.netlify.app/index.html</link><description/><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ignasia.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blog</title><link>https://ignasia.netlify.app/blog/index.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ignasia.netlify.app/blog/index.html</guid><description>Stay updated with the latest insights, trends, and best practices in cybersecurity, risk management, and governance from the experts at Ignasia Consulting.</description></item><item><title>About Us</title><link>https://ignasia.netlify.app/about/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ignasia.netlify.app/about/index.html</guid><description>Ignasia Consulting is an independent, values-driven consultancy dedicated to strengthening trust, resilience, and positive impact in a rapidly changing world.
Founded by industry veterans, our mission is to help organisations unlock their full potential while navigating the complex landscape of cyber risk, regulatory change, and operational challenges.
Beyond its team, Ignasia also boasts of a wide and diverse network of professionals and industry experts providing us access to a vast pool of knowledge and skills.</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>https://ignasia.netlify.app/contact/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ignasia.netlify.app/contact/index.html</guid><description>At IGNASIA Consulting, clear communication is our priority. Whether you’re exploring governance, risk, and compliance solutions or ready to dive into a project, we’re here to support you every step of the way.
Reach Out ✉️ Email: info@ignasia.in
📞 Phone: +91 8971 21 2227
🏢 Address: Future Knowledge Labs, Bengaluru 560102, India
Begin with a Free GRC Self-Assessment Take our 25-question assessment benchmarking your GRC maturity against ISO 27001, NIST CSF, and CIS Controls. Instant insights and tailored guidance.</description></item><item><title>Meet Our Expert Team</title><link>https://ignasia.netlify.app/team/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ignasia.netlify.app/team/index.html</guid><description>At IGNASIA Consulting, our strength lies in our people. Our team combines deep technical expertise, premier consulting experience, and a shared commitment to creating a kinder, more secure digital future. Each member brings verified certifications and proven track records that collectively deliver world-class GRC solutions.
Our Collective Strength Combined Experience: 35+ years across cybersecurity, risk management, and GRC consulting
Industry Expertise:
Banking, Financial Services &amp; Insurance (BFSI) Technology and SaaS platforms Energy and manufacturing sectors Healthcare and life sciences Government and regulatory bodies Service Excellence:</description></item><item><title>Our Services</title><link>https://ignasia.netlify.app/services/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ignasia.netlify.app/services/index.html</guid><description>At IGNASIA Consulting, we deliver governance, risk, and compliance excellence through three core service pillars designed to protect, optimise, and transform your organisation.
1. AUDIT Independent assurance and certification readiness
ISO 27001 Audit &amp; Certification Services Gap analysis against ISO 27001:2022 requirements Internal audit services and management reviews Pre-certification readiness assessments External certification support and ongoing surveillance ISMS documentation review and validation Regulatory Compliance Audits RBI, IRDAI, SEBI compliance assessments DPDP Act and GDPR compliance audits SOC 2 Type I and Type II readiness Third-party vendor security assessments Privacy impact assessments (PIAs) Information Security Audits Comprehensive security posture assessments Vulnerability assessments and penetration testing readiness Cloud security configuration reviews Access control and privilege management audits Data governance and classification audits 2. CONSULTING Strategic advisory and implementation services</description></item><item><title>Social Impact</title><link>https://ignasia.netlify.app/social-impact/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ignasia.netlify.app/social-impact/index.html</guid><description>At IGNASIA Consulting, our mission extends beyond providing exceptional cybersecurity and GRC services. We believe technology and security should empower organisations to create lasting positive change in society.
Our Commitment We are dedicated to supporting purpose-driven organisations—from NGOs and nonprofits to social enterprises—that strive for a better world. Through our expertise, resources, and partnerships, we enable these organisations to strengthen their cyber-resilience and governance frameworks, so they can focus on what matters most: making an impact.</description></item></channel></rss>