<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Meet Our Expert Team :: Ignasia Consulting</title><link>https://ignasia.netlify.app/team/index.html</link><description>At IGNASIA Consulting, our strength lies in our people. Our team combines deep technical expertise, premier consulting experience, and a shared commitment to creating a kinder, more secure digital future. Each member brings verified certifications and proven track records that collectively deliver world-class GRC solutions.
Our Collective Strength Combined Experience: 35+ years across cybersecurity, risk management, and GRC consulting
Industry Expertise:
Banking, Financial Services &amp; Insurance (BFSI) Technology and SaaS platforms Energy and manufacturing sectors Healthcare and life sciences Government and regulatory bodies Service Excellence:</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ignasia.netlify.app/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Abhishek Divakar</title><link>https://ignasia.netlify.app/team/abhishek-divakar/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ignasia.netlify.app/team/abhishek-divakar/index.html</guid><description>Abhishek is the visionary leader behind IGNASIA Consulting, bringing over 12 years of expertise in information security, risk management, and GRC advisory. His journey spans prestigious organisations including PwC India and Wipro’s award-winning audit function, where he pioneered innovative security solutions and led enterprise-wide cybersecurity initiatives.</description></item><item><title>Shalu Jain</title><link>https://ignasia.netlify.app/team/shalu-jain/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ignasia.netlify.app/team/shalu-jain/index.html</guid><description>Shalu brings over 10 years of enterprise security excellence and GRC platform mastery. Her expertise in RSA Archer development, combined with comprehensive security management experience at Sony and Wipro, makes her instrumental in delivering automated, scalable security solutions.</description></item><item><title>Akshita Satish</title><link>https://ignasia.netlify.app/team/akshita-satish/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ignasia.netlify.app/team/akshita-satish/index.html</guid><description>Akshita represents the next generation of cybersecurity professionals, combining rigorous technical training with creative problem-solving perspectives from her unique multi-domain background. Her fresh approach to traditional security challenges brings innovative solutions to complex GRC requirements.</description></item><item><title>Dolly Kumar</title><link>https://ignasia.netlify.app/team/dolly-kumar/index.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ignasia.netlify.app/team/dolly-kumar/index.html</guid><description>Dolly drives operational excellence and client success at IGNASIA, bringing entrepreneurial leadership and proven business development expertise. Her experience spans business operations, project management, and strategic growth across multiple industries, with a deep commitment to social impact initiatives.
Key Achievements Founder of Eternity Landscapes (sustainable landscape solutions) ₹1 crore+ monthly revenue generation at Newton School 98% on-time delivery rate across 100+ international projects 25% improvement in customer retention through strategic frameworks</description></item></channel></rss>